benzworld.org 2006-04-17

# BenzWorld Terms of Use

|   
---  
| 

* * *

About us  
Terms of Use  
Privacy Policy

* * *

**Terms of Use and Privacy Policy**

Your membership is bound by these documents so please read them carefully.

Any questions should be directed to info@benzworld.org and we will reply promptly. 

* * *

* * *  
  
---  
BenzWorld's website content, articles and publications are not endorsed or affiliated with Mercedes-Benz AG, Mercedes-Benz  
USA, or Daimler Chrysler

No photos, articles, graphics, or BenzWorld.org logos may be used or reproduced without written permission.

BenzWorld.org can be contacted at 

All website content  
Copyright ©  
1999-2006  
BenzWorld.org

Last Update:  
November 24, 2003

Terms of Use  
Privacy Policy  

|  |  **Privacy Policy**  
---  
**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how BenzWorld.org treats personal information that BenzWorld.org collects and receives, including information related to your past use of BenzWorld.org products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that BenzWorld.org does not own or control, or to people that BenzWorld.org does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

**      General**

  * BenzWorld.org collects personal information **only** when you register and/or edit your profile with BenzWorld.org.
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender,  occupation  and personal interests and will be **displayed only** when you choose to.  Once you register with BenzWorld.org and sign in to our services, only the options you select as public will be displayed but you are not anonymous to us.
  * BenzWorld.org automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, BenzWorld.org cookie information, and the page you request.
  * BenzWorld.org uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the site resouces and content you see, fulfill your requests, improve our services, contact you in case you violate the Terms of Use, to conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure  
**

  * BenzWorld.org will **never  ** rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies **except** to provide site services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of BenzWorld.org's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
    * We transfer information about you if BenzWorld.org is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, BenzWorld.org will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  

  * BenzWorld.org **does not** provide any personal information to any advertiser or sponsor when you interact with or view a targeted ad. 
  * BenzWorld.org advertisers include Mercedes-Benz related companies only.

**Cookies**

  * BenzWorld.org stores only **one** cookie and is set only when you choose to have the site log you in automatically.
  * Other companies' (i.e. advertisers and sponsors) use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies **do not** have access to BenzWorld.org's cookies.

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We **limit** access to personal information about you to BenzWorld staff who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
  * Your BenzWorld Account Information is password-protected.
